

# Frontend Engineer UX Designer

### **Contact**

### Mail

reyesg.juani@gmail.com

### **Phone**

+591 75809992

#### LinkedIn

/juanireyes

### **Education**

#### 2021

# Professional Diploma in UX Design

UX Design Institute, Glasgow Caledonian University

2015 - 2020

# Bachelor's Degree In **Systems** Engineering

Universidad Católica Boliviana "San Pablo"

## Languages

Spanish Native
English C1
Portuguese B2
Russian A3

### **Skills**



### **Profile**

Hey there! I'm Juani, a 25 years old bolivian Frontend Developer and UX Designer. With +3 years of professional experience within multiple US enterprises, projects and applications. I consider myself as a really friendly, cheerful and positive guy, who is always willing to learn new technologies and experiences. So tell me, how can I help you?

## **Work Experience**

#### **Dreamcode**

### **Lead Frontend Developer**

**2021 - Present** 

Working for Omedym. Refactored an application from scratch using Vite bundler with React and Typescript. I'm currently handling and refactoring multiple workspace applications including a components library. And I'm leading the frontend development of the team.

#### **New Vision Data**

### **Frontend Developer**

2019 - 2021

Worked for multiple US companies, such as Zebra Technologies and MHFD. Worked with React and Typescript among different map tools (Mapbox and Openlayers). Led a real-time player tracking feature for a NFL project using real-time data and map layers.

### **DACorp Soft**

### **Frontend Developer Internship**

2018

Led the development of an e-commerce site using Angular. Also, learned the basics for enterprise software development with the usage of services and microservices.

## **Projects**

### Pick N' Pay

### **Software Engineer - UX/UI Designer**

2021

Built an administrators and clients systems for this startup. Designed the application using Figma and developed it with NextJs and Firebase.